The mission to save Christmas is on.
Red One is a action, comedy, fantasy film directed by Jake Kasdan.
After Santa Claus (codename: Red One) is kidnapped, the North Pole's Head of Security must team up with the
world's most infamous tracker in a globe-trotting, action-packed mission to save Christmas.
Callum Drift, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Jack O'Malley, played by Chris Evans.
Zoe, played by Lucy Liu.
Nick, played by J.K. Simmons.
Gryla, played by Kiernan Shipka.
Mrs. Claus, played by Bonnie Hunt.
Red One is a 2024 American Christmas action comedy film
directed by Jake Kasdan and written by Chris Morgan.
It stars Dwayne Johnson, Chris Evans, Lucy Liu, and J.
Simmons, with Kiernan Shipka, Bonnie Hunt, Kristofer Hivju, Nick
Kroll, and Wesley Kimmel appearing in supporting roles.
The film tells the story of Head of North Pole Security Callum Drift, who teams up with
black-hat hacker Jack O'Malley to locate a kidnapped Santa Claus on Christmas Eve.
Principal photography for the film began in October 2022 and concluded in
February 2023, with filming locations including Atlanta.
Red One was first released theatrically by Warner Bros.
Pictures internationally on November 6, 2024, and in the United
States by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer on November 15.
The film received mostly negative reviews from critics and was a box-office
bomb, grossing $186 million against a budget of $200–$250 million.
The film explores themes of rescue, bounty hunter,
holiday, kidnapping, santa claus.
The tone is lighthearted.